sporticos.com 2019-04-25

# Read our privacy policy before you start using Sporticos.

Sporticos.com aims to deliver information and data as accurate and fast as possible, however we are not responsible for inaccurate and delayed content. You are not allowed to copy, download, reproduce, republish, frame, broadcast, transmit in any manner whatsoever, unless there is express written consent given by Sporticos.com and there is a clear link back to "Sporticos.com." Any activity against this Article will be viewed as a direct violation of our policy. 

## What information do we collect?

In Sporticos.com we collect information from you only when you subscribe to our newsletter. Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. 

## What does Sporticos.com use your information for?

Any of the information Sporticos.com collects from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience
  * To improve our website
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

## How does Sporticos.com protect your information?

Sporticos.com implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

## Cookies

Cookies are small text files that a site can place on your computer or mobile device to store certain information. We use cookies to keep track of how you use our website, make our website work efficiently, and deliver relevant content including advertisement. 

You can set up your browser not to allow cookies, however some parts our site would not function properly. You can get more information about cookies here: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website, such as Google Analytics and Facebook plugin. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. Sporticos.com have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

## Your Consent

By using Sporticos.com, you consent to our website’s privacy policy. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on August 27, 2015.
